<resources>
    <string name="app_name">2020</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="facebook_application_id" translatable="false">513844805913776</string>
    <string name="facebook_login_protocol_scheme" translatable="false">fb513844805913776</string>
    <string name="temp">The Golghar or Gol Ghar (गोलघर), ("Round house") is a large granary located to the west of the Gandhi Maidan in Patna, capital of Bihar state, India.
    The Golghar or Gol Ghar (गोलघर), ("Round house") is a large granary located to the west of the Gandhi Maidan in Patna, capital o
        The Golghar or Gol Ghar (गोलघर), ("Round house") is a large granary located to the west of the Gandhi Maidan in Patna, capital o
    </string>
    <string name="about">This app offers the detailed history and relevant information about the
popular Indian places and tourism ideas. The main motto is to create awareness about our rich culture and heritage among
 the local residents.It is designed user friendly, so that more and more number of citizens can be benefited. The app contains
a number of dazzling photos and articles about Indian tourism such as natural beauty,geographic wonders,
local customs, historic sites, diverse culture and arts of India. It offers an additional feature in which
 user can suggest to add the places which can be converted into tourist spots and hence can promote business which will lead to the growth of
 economy. It also uses Google Earth so that users can
get the 3d view of the landmark. It also provides an excellent picture analyzing framework in which you can capture an image of the landmark from
your camera and the app will give details about that landmark. There are more than 500+ tourist destinations in our app which are
classified in different categories like state wise, latest trends.</string>
    <string name="about_city"><u>About City</u></string>
    <string name="physical_artifacts"><u>Physical Artifacts</u></string>
    <string name="practices"><u>Practices/Culture</u></string>
    <string name="skills"><u>Skills/Knowledge</u></string>


</resources>
